Once upon a time, there was a girl
named Tessa who had a dream.
This is a story about her reality.
Better hurry, Tessa.
The wicked wltch just arrived.
Tessa! Tessa!
It's all right. I've got this.
Thanks, Joe.
Hey, maybe she gets nicer on vacation.
Holy crappola, Tessa!
You've scuffed my favorite bag!
I'm sorry, Divine.
Uh, this is a lot to carry.
Well, we're all pitching in, Tessa.
- I'll bring the cart. Sir, can I...
- Uh-uh. Uh-uh.
No! No way am I tipping those vultures.
No! No!
Oh. Oh. Oh.
Be extra careful of Sparkles.
Who's a good dog? Who's a good dog?
- Divine?
- What? Yes?
He's dead.
Not in my heart, Tessa.
Mom! The VIP Princess Package
Includes a costume party,
and Reed West is performing.
Let me see!
Olympia, must you...
Even better, we get our own private
1-minute Reed West encounter.
We're in it for a lot more than 7 minutes,
Athena. We're here to win.
Okay, I'll be there in a minute.
Oh, a pool! Athena, you need to put
on your bikini and sit by that pool.
- Okay.
- Not you, Olympia.
Oh, my God!
These girls look like pros.
They don't have superstar's blood
coursing through their veins.
Remember, girls,
you're Madonna's third cousins.
Twice removed.
It's not a lot of blood.
Blood is blood.
If I were 10 years younger,
I'd snag that role myself.
Uh-oh.
Janet's here.
Her parents sent her
to music camp In New York.
See you ladies at the VIP lunch.
Can't wait!
Oh, Bianca's here, too.
Lauren!
Divine!
I almost didn't recognize you
with your new face.
Would like the number?
They do lipo as well.
I've forgotten
how dreadfully witty you are.
So we're really excited about this week,
right, Blanca?
Bianca? Sweetheart? Darling?
Bianca. Sweetheart.
Yeah, I'm so excited.
She's a bit of a slug, isn't she?
No, she's been rehearsing.
You've only brought one assistant.
So brave.
Oh, I'm not her assistant.
I'm her stepdaughter.
- Uh, Tessa?
- Yeah?
Could you please go get Sparkles?
- Get Sparkles!
- Yes, right away, Divine.
Thank you.
She's a bit sensitive
about her position In life.
Well, it's been fascinating,
but now I'm bored.
- Tessa, we're on the move!
- Right away!
Oh, Reed! I would sell body parts for you.
Good ones.
Argh, gross! Stop drooling, Olympia.
Argh.
He's definitely worth a kidney.
He looks taken. Who's the girl?
Argh. Harper Halston.
The heiress.
She's so pretty.
Her family owns Royal Lagoons Resorts.
They're holding the audition contest.
You'd know all this if you weren't so busy
greasing up carburetors or whatever.
- You mean my job.
- Not this week, Tessa.
You're here to help Athena and Olympia
focus on one thing.
Dazzling Reed and winning the lead role.
One of you girls is going
to star in the musical,
win that recording contract,
and do me proud.
I named you after goddesses for a reason.
What's the musical?
- Cinderella.
Okay, that's kind of ironic.
You, follow me.
Yes, ma'am.
You are going to love
your little room.
- It's right this way.
- Okay, all right.
This is like having your own spa.
Right through here.
Here we go.
Nice and cozy under the stairs.
So I'm Harry Potter.
Exactly.
Now, um, be careful of the gate
because it locks from the outside,
and don't tell anyone you're here, okay?
Oh, I'm gonna get
Into so much trouble for this.
Don't worry.
It's not exactly something I'll instagram.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Olympia, stop that!
That's disgusting. Stop It!
Oh, my God! What are you doing?
Stop it! Don't eat that.
Don't you dare put that In your mouth!
I cannot believe
you humiliate me this way.
Oh, dear.
Oh...
Hello. Hello.
- Not really ready, yeah.
- I think you have this In the bag.
I've never seen
such a dull group of girls.
You remember Janet?
- Oh, yes. Jane. Hello.
- It's Janet.
Oh, you dropped...
Oh.
Whoops.
- Whoops.
- Tessa. Tessa. Ah!
- Ow!
Tessa.
Ah.
Ladies...
- Oh, thank you so much.
- Lovely.
She's just a little slow,
but, you know, she smells good,
so we keep her around.
Well, she's learning.
You're so bad!
Hello! Hello! Welcome, VIPs!
You know, by the looks of this crowd,
you'd think VIP stands
for very beautiful person.
I guess then It'd be VBP, but...
Uh, thank you!
Welcome, everyone!
I'm Freddy Marks, the director,
and you all know pop sensation Reed West.
Hi. It's lovely to be here.
I discovered Reed on YouTube,
and now I'm hoping to find a brand new
star right here In this very room.
Harper sang a romantic duet with Reed.
Will you be next?
Now, auditions will be held
tomorrow morning,
and the show will premiere on
the very last night of your VIP stay.
So this is gonna be a fast-paced,
exciting adventure
for all those who make the cast,
especially one very lucky young lady.
And the best part,
if our Cinderella impresses
the Slick Tracks record execs,
she'll be signed on the spot.
Yeah, how about that?
All right, so good luck, everybody,
and we?! see you all In the morning.
- Thank you.
- Cheers.
Earth to Tessa.
Oh. Mom, help. Help!
Mom, I'm drowning.
I'm drowning.
- Oh!
- Help.
Sorry. Give me one second.
Grab this.
She's so funny when she's drowning.
R's so great.
Gently, Tessa.
Can you do my face?
Am I getting it all?
Hmm, yeah, just...
I think you missed a spot just right...
- There?
- Yeah, right there.
- Is that it?
- Oh, yeah.
We wouldn't want you to get sunburned.
- Okay.
- Good, you can go now.
Okay.
Spritz.
Great song, huh?
Yes, it's beautiful.
Oh, I'm Georgie, by the way.
I'm the makeup artist for the show.
Uh, I'm Tessa,
currently an indentured servant.
But you sing, too.
I heard you humming.
No...
I mean, yeah, I love music and dance,
but maybe In another life.
Too bad we only get one.
Um...
It was nice to meet you.
- All right, here we go.
- All right.
Hey.
Is that a 500cc twin? 1950, right?
Yeah, if you say so. Can you just...
Yeah, we're stage hands,
not really bike people.
Turn. Turn right. Turn.
- Come on.
- Wait.
- Here we go.
- All right, we got this.
Wow.
Wow, that's one of Lambini's very first
real sporting V-Twin engines.
She's... She's beautiful.
You have any idea why
one of these sporting things won't start?
You know what? I'd love to figure it out.
Hey, can I borrow those?
My Pants?
Yeah, your overalls.
- Yeah. I mean, yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
Start her up.
There we go.
Nice work, Tessa.
Oh, they got the bike started.
I wish I was there.
You could give me a ride.
Yeah, the alignment was just off.
The two cylinders kind of needed to run
as one, but It's all good now.
All right, brilliant. Thanks, mate.
"Mate."
Reedsiboo, can I finish my story?
I have lunch with Kim In Paris.
Yeah, sure, sure.
Guys, thanks so much.
Freddy will cover you.
Okay. Just...
No. Um...
I've got to go, guys,
but I'll see you later.
- Yeah.
- Let me know how the bike goes, okay?
- Than ks.
- Than ks. Yeah.
"Some days, I've worked so hard,
"my body aches like that of an old woman.
"My face is covered in cinders.
"My feet..."
Hey, Picasso,
can you color inside the lines'?
Could you hold still?
Me next!
All right, Sparkles, I need your opinion
on a very Important subject.
What do you think?
Candy Yum-Yum or Lady Danger?
You rascal, you!
All right, Lady Danger It ls.
Tessa, save Sparkles!
Sparkles is drowning!
He's drowning! He's drowning!
Don't use too much product, Tessa.
Fluffy but not pretentious.
Hi. Can I...
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Hey, Tessa, come on over.
Hey.
- Eddie.
- Let me get this for you.
Hey, guys... Thank you very much.
Hi.
Hey.
Shh.
My God, they're amazing!
Hey.
Biggest secret here, the best talent
makes beds and hauls trash.
Wow.
Come on, Tessa. Let's go dance. Come on.
- What?
- Go. Go!
Okay.
That was sick!
That's crazy, girl. Come on.
Show us some more moves.
- What?
- Come on! Show us your moves!
Now it's your turn, Georgie.
Get back to work. Come on. Move. Move!
Why are you not auditioning
for the musical?
Thanks, Georgie, but my stepmother
would never, ever allow me to audition.
That's it.
- What?
- Audition In disguise.
Okay, I'm sure you're great with makeup
and your brushes and stuff, but I doubt...
Pout for me.
I'm not so sure about this.
Shush, shush, and shush.
Yeah, let's begin.
Bull's eye.
Oh, hey, Georgie, who's your friend?
- You know me. I'm...
- She's a guest, Eddie.
She's a guest. You need anything,
you just... You let us know.
I can sweep. Sweep your room.
We sweep... We sweep rooms. We...
He didn't recognize me,
and I've worn his coveralls before.
Okay, don't know what that means,
but I feel vindicated.
Now you have to audition.
Georgie, look, your makeup brushes
are like magic wands, but I can't do this.
My family will
recognize my voice Immediately.
Then disguise it. Here we are.
It's not like, "I'm Olympia!"
It's like,
"I'm Olympia. I'm here. I'm yours."
Okay, I'm going-
- I'm gonna do this.
- Okay, go.
Okay, I'm gonna go.
- Tess, go.
- Okay.
You're not listening to me.
Wow, Janet, you look great,
and don't worry.
No one will even notice that huge vein
bulging out of your forehead.
Young lady.
Are you a VIP guest?
I didn't see you at the brunch.
Um...
The trolley broke.
The trolley?
Yes, it's a bloody shame.
The trolley broke.
I know you from somewhere.
No, um, I don't think so.
The Niedermeyer Bar Mitzvah?
Did we Hava Nagila?
I don't think I had that pleasure, ma'am.
- Oh, you didn't have that pleasure.
- No.
Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
The National Dog Show in Philly?
Afraid not. I'm a cat person.
- You even smell familiar.
- It's vanilla!
It's my deodorant.
It's all the rage In London, England.
Very interesting.
- All right.
- Yes.
I've got my eyes on you.
Oh, that won't be necessary. It's okay.
Cheers!
God save the Queen
in London,
where I'm from.
Whatever. All right, Olympia...
Oh, that was close.
She has a big finish.
Okay, thank you, dear.
Next.
A little louder, please?
Prepare to be amazed.
Faster. Faster.
No, no! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Okay. Go ahead.
Ah...
Right.
What doth ye lads fancy?
What do we doth fancy, Freddy?
You're supposed to come prepared, sweetie.
Right.
Just one second.
Could you please play
Stuck on the Outside for me?
Thank you.
Well, it's pretty average.
What's your name?
Uh...
- Cinderella.
- Cinderella?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Oh.
- Ironic. Hmm.
- Just a bit.
I like your top.
I've got a pair of boxers like those.
Go London. Patriotic.
Whereabouts are you from?
I can't quite find your accent.
You can't? It's odd.
I'm from... It's a small farming village.
It's just north of London. It's called...
It's called Yorkshirer Puddingshire.
- Yorkshire Puddingshire?
- Yorkshirer.
- Yorkshirer Puddingshire.
- Mmm-hmm.
Yes.
Okay. Oh, is that near...
Uh-huh.
It's right near Hogwartshire.
Hogwartshire, Freddy. I knew it.
Yeah. Okay.
Well, Yorkshire Puddingshire,
let's see If you can move.
- You want me to dance?
- Yeah, I'd love you to dance.
- Are you ready?
- For what?
Whoa!
- Can you salsa?
- Oh, not at all.
- Catch me.
- Catch you?
Who the hell is she?
- It's hard to say.
- Why does she get to dance?
"Hard to say." She's an impostor.
She wasn't even at the kick-off brunch.
She's here now.
- I'm so sorry. I have to go.
- What?
No, wait. You're amazing. Wait.
Arrest that girl! She's impersonating
a VIP! Arrest that girl!
Grab her! Don't let her get away!
Don't let her get away!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop that!
Well, I guess
the fairy tale gods have spoken.
The way you two danced together!
- It was like a fairy tale.
- I bet he's gonna pick you.
It doesn't matter. You saw Divine.
She'd get me disqualified In a heartbeat.
We'll come up with a fake name,
and It'll all work out.
Georgie, I'm really sorry.
I really appreciate
everything you've done for me...
But I think it's time for me
to get back to my real life.
But thank you.
Sit up straight. Sit up straight.
All right, I'd just like to start off
by saying
thank you very much to everyone here
for auditioning today.
We'll be posting a cast list soon
of the secondary roles,
but I've found my Cinderella.
Now I just need to actually find her.
The mystery Cinderella, she lost
her dance shoe today at the audition.
It's a very special shoe.
Uh, if you're the owner
of that matching shoe,
then please come forward
by midnight tomorrow.
And the role is yours.
Thank you.
Go! Go! Go! Out of my way! Out of my way!
Excuse me. Follow me.
Try to keep up. Try to keep up.
Coming through!
- This one?
- No.
- I'm not sure.
Think, Olympia. Round up every last
little brain cell that's In there.
Good morning.
- This one?
- No.
- Th is one?
- Walt.
Yes, that's the shoe flower.
That's the one.
Oh, Tessa, you need to paint that flower
on this shoe.
Um...
There's no point
because If he has the matching...
Nobody else knows
about the hand-painted flower.
He has to pick somebody by midnight.
- Go! Go! Go!
- Okay.
Guess what? Get Loose
just made the Billboard Hot 100!
Wow, that was fast.
See? I told you that to work with Harper
would be gold for your career.
It's Reed!
If anybody is interested,
the supporting cast list
has just been posted backstage.
Come on, let's go.
Okay, I tried, but I just really
don't think this is gonna work. It's...
What happened? Did someone die?
Worse. Bianca got cast as fairy godmother.
Janet is the evil stepmother,
and all we get to play ls
- the ugly stepsisters.
- Ugly stepsisters.
How could they possibly think
that we should play
those mean, horrible, self-absorbed girls!
Gosh, it boggles the imagination,
doesn't It?
Finally.
What, did you paint it with your toes?
As usual, I'll take care of things,
right, girls?
Uh, hello? Doorbell.
Olympia, sit up straight.
Athena, stop looking so depressed.
It's from Reed West.
"Reed West requests the company of..."
No!
What is it? What's wrong?
You! Why does he want to see you?
What?
I saw you at Reed's announcement,
making gooey eyes at him.
No, that's...
You plucked your eyebrows for him,
didn't you?
No, I didn't. I didn't. It's just
a big misunderstanding. It's just...
Well, we'll find out, shall we?
Come with me.
Girls! Girls, we're leaving.
"I don't want to go!"
We're gonna get to the bottom of this
right now, little missy,
and if you screwed things up
for my girls, I...
- Girls, try to keep up!
- That's R.
Reed? Reed West?
I have Tessa here. You wanted to see her?
Wait.
Oh, yes, been trying to track you down.
You have?
Why would you want to see her?
- Why, I just need your help.
- You do?
- The show kind of depends on it.
- It does'?
Yeah.
What is... The mechanic said you were
the one who got Lt started yesterday.
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
I'm sorry for mistaking you for a dude.
It's my bad.
It's okay.
I'm just glad every/thing's all cleared up.
Right. Well, there's...
Yeah, there's a little clunking noise
coming from the...
Uh...
From the motorcycle.
- From the bike?
- Yeah.
- Um, could you describe the clunking?
- Like a...
Okay, is it like a fast...
Like a...
Kind of. Well, it starts off...
It starts off like It's building,
- so it's a bit more...
- Okay, like a...
No, it's more like a...
- Like a train.
- I don't know what trains you've heard.
Yes, it cuts out,
and If I try and do It again, It goes...
Yeah, I think I know it.
Well, we just need
to get It fixed, If we can.
Otherwise, Cinderella
won't have a pumpkin carriage.
I can try.
Wait, wait, wait.
If I let my darling Tessa do this for you,
you have to do something for me.
You have to let
my talented daughters audition again.
They had an eensy problem the first time.
By the way,
prepare to have your mind blown.
Uh...
Yeah, deal.
Come on, girls, we have to practice.
- Bye, Reed.
- Bye.
Olympia!
Freddy, can we set Tessa up
In the prop room, please?
It's not bad as it looks. I swear.
Well, this is nothing compared
to the hot mess I just saw.
I'm sure.
I kind of overheard a little bit.
Okay, so these are the parts
that I need you to get
so that I can fix your pumpkin carriage.
Where did you learn to do all this?
Um, my dad was a race car driver.
Yeah, he had his own repair shop,
so I was basically working on cars
before I could walk.
Is your dad still racing cars now?
I hope so. In heaven.
Could you pass me the 9/16 spanner?
- No.
- Oh, the wrench.
Oh...
- No, I don't know what that one...
- The small silver thing...
- This one? Small silver thingy.
- Mmm-hmm. Yeah, right there.
- Should've just said that.
- Thanks.
So did your dad let
baby Tessa drive race cars, too?
No.
No, I had to wait
till I was about five for that.
All right, wise to wait. Oh.
- Hi.
- You did it, babel
The show's sold out. The resort, too.
Dad's thrilled.
Oh, that's great.
Freddy says
you haven't cast Cinderella yet?
No, not yet, but there's someone
we're hoping is gonna accept It.
Then make it happen, hot stuff.
Anyway, got to fly.
- Sorry. It's a lot going on.
- It's okay.
I'm in trouble if this girl doesn't show.
You really think
your mystery girl is that good?
Oh, definitely, but Royal Resorts want us
to complete casting today.
Yeah, and if mystery girl
doesn't come forward,
then we have to pick someone else.
I like spending time with you.
I'd really like it
If you'd meet me tomorrow,
and maybe, well,
you'd let me hold your spanner.
Oh, my God! I thought he was gonna be,
like, all abs and attitude,
but he's so sweet.
Someone's crushing hard.
Oh, please!
He's dating a gorgeous celebrity heiress.
Who can't possibly hold a candle to you.
She doesn't have to.
She has people for that.
It's okay. It's just the way things are.
Yeah, I wish...
What?
Your dad,
he made his dreams come true, right'?
Yeah.
Wouldn't he want you to do the same?
I just hate to see
perfectly good dreams go to waste.
Okay, Dad, I'll be brave.
Come on.
How much longer is this going to take?
- We got to get moving.
- I don't know.
- Where's the girl with the shoe?
Look, she's not coming.
Can we just pick someone?
No, it's not midnight yet.
Just a few more minutes.
Stop it. Stop it!
Stop it.
So annoying.
Unbelievable.
Reed, if we don't pick someone,
they'll cancel my show. Please?
Fine.
Am I too late?
- That's her, right?
- Yeah.
- Hello.
Cherry blossoms
were me mum's favorite flowers.
Why did you run?
I wasn't sure
I should've auditioned at all.
But you've changed your mind, right?
You'll be my Cinderella?
Yes.
Hold on a second!
Walt one minute!
Hold on! Hold on! I have something to say!
This girl, I bet she's not even
a legitimate guest.
What? That's absurd.
Ah! "Absurd!"
Of course I'm probably a guest.
Well, what's your name?
- My name?
- Yes.
Right, because everyone...
Everyone has a name, right'?
Spit it out.
Mmm-hmm. Um...
The... See, the name
that my mother gave me was...
Bella!
- Bella Snow!
- Bella Buckingham.
- Bella Buckingham?
- Bella Snow!
It's Bella Buckingham Snow.
Bella Snow for short.
It's good to see you.
I was just at your mom's castle...
In Yorkshire Puddingshire. How lovely.
Yup, Bella Snow, VIP. She's legit.
- Thank you.
- Okay, a“ fight.
I'm on to you.
You and your silly sneakers
had better watch your step.
Okay, then. Read this.
Check out the links.
Learn the routines.
Start rehearsal In the morning.
All right.
No! No carbs for you.
You're getting too fat.
Here's the tablet you requested.
Finally. Sit down.
I want you to Google something.
- Okay, what do you want me to Google?
- Google Bella Snow.
- Snow.
- Bella Snow.
Snow, like the stuff
that falls from the sky.
B-E-L...
Just give that to me. Let me do it.
- You're so slow.
- You do it. She's too slow.
Okay.
Okay, here's one.
"Bella Snow, uh, dentist In New Jersey."
That's not her.
That girl is as brainless as they come.
Okay, I found a British Bella Snow
who died 100 years ago.
- Aw!
- This is pointless. She doesn't exist.
I knew it! She's an impostor.
I want you to follow her after rehearsal
and find out who she ls.
Me?
- Oh, I'll go, too.
- Can I go?
I'm gonna go make sure the chef
has your suggestions for dinner, okay?
All right, and, you know, I want
the spritzing station by the cabana today.
- Got it.
- I love to be spritzed.
Just go with what you're feeling
at the time.
- Don't decide beforehand.
- All right.
Just let it be whatever you're feeling
In the moment, okay?
- Yeah.
- Cool.
- Oh, good, you're here. Okay.
- HI.
So we want to do
Cinderella's opening song.
You're ready, right?
Okay, great!
Let's give her some space, folks!
Right, this song's about a girl who
lives a difficult life filled with loss,
who struggles to find
the courage to go after her dreams.
Try and imagine
what that might be like, okay?
I can try.
Okay, places everybody.
We definitely found our girl.
Okay.
Seventeen.
Arms up. up, up, up.
- Sorry. Sorry.
- Mmm.
Oh, you've got a waist
like a little hummingbird.
- Okay.
- Cheers.
Bella.
Georgie.
Look at you, all princessy.
For the first time,
I feel like maybe I can do this,
like for real.
Hello.
Argh! My God. My stepsisters
are waiting to follow me outside.
Go out the back. They won't expect it.
- You sure?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Okay, I'm gonna go.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Where is she?
Come on.
Okay, you go that way.
Got you!
Oops.
Who are you?
- Got you!
- Olympia!
- Oh, it's such a delight to see you here.
- It is'?
Could you be so kind as to pass me
that suntan lotion over there, dear?
We Brits, we just crisp so easily.
Oh, do you mind? I can't reach.
Thank you.
So, tell me, Olympia, was it hard
to get all those scarves In your mouth?
- Oh, I had to train my cheeks for weeks.
- Did you?
- Do you want to see?
- Sure.
That's a lot of grapes.
Do you know what would be lovely?
Some lemonade.
- Hmm and snacks.
- Yes, and snacks.
- I can get them.
- Oh, you could?
- That's absolutely perfect.
- Mmm-hmm. Okay.
Thank you. I'll be just right here
waiting. Right here. Won't move.
She's so nice and smart.
But then she disappeared
before I could give her her snacks.
You got played, Olympia.
You're just jealous because
Bella's head is prettier than yours.
Where have you been?
I was just picking up
the dresses you ordered.
Are these for the costume ball?
We're going as Cinderellas.
'Lee-haw.
Creative.
Abracadabra!
Just... That's what a magician says.
So this is your wand.
It's very simple to use.
I'll just demonstrate for you.
Ah, Gino, could you step
Into Cinderella's position, please?
Yeah.
So all you do is... Twirl.
See? It's so easy.
Just a flick of the wrist.
Here. Go ahead, uh, get a feel for it,
and let me know If you have any questions.
Sorry.
This is ridiculous.
What were you thinking getting
Blanca and the stepsisters In the show?
Olympia, stop it! Gross!
We have no choice, all right?
The VIP Package guarantees them
supporting roles.
Don't worry. It'll be fine.
I can get a great performance
out of anybody.
These wings are so heavy.
She's gonna be great.
So it's four beats in the hips.
All right?
- Hello.
- Oh, Bella is here,
so let's rehearse
the shoe-fitting scene, please.
No.
Yes, that's what we're gonna do.
Freddy, can you run the show
without me for a little bit?
What? Why? Where are you going?
To fix Cinderella's pumpkin carriage.
Can't do the show without It, right?
Ah...
Guess I'll stand in.
If Tessa is not there,
he'll think she's a flake or doesn't care.
You can't be in two places at once.
Meet me in makeup
with coveralls and a cap, okay?
Okay.
Tess, how are you going to pull this off?
Great question. I think I'm going to get
Reed started, then tell him I have to go,
and then I'll just meet you
back here with the Bella wig.
You work your magic again
with your magic makeup hands.
- Okay.
- Other shoe.
Thanks.
Okay. Ah...
wig. okay-
- You need a brush?
- No, It's okay. I don't need a brush.
Okay.
Time to go.
Ew, ew!
Okay. Cap.
- Here. Here you go.
- Okay.
Good? Okay. Bye-bye.
Go! Go!
“Okay
- Go!
Oh, thank God. I thought you forgot.
No, it just takes a little time
to look this hot.
Yeah?
Sorry.
I got those parts that you asked for.
I don't know...
Oh, wow. That's amazing.
- That or Legos.
- Um...
Wow, I'm surprised
you got these parts so quickly.
Yeah, well, the perks of being a pop star.
Must be nice.
Not really.
But nobody should have to listen
to pop star problems.
Like getting everything you could want,
Including awesome bike parts?
Yeah. Not exactly.
Or like not being able
to follow your heart, maybe?
Ah...
I heard those songs
that you wrote for the musical.
They're really good. Beautiful.
Really?
- Honestly?
- Honestly.
That's the real you, right?
Freddy just thinks
I need to stick to my brand
until my career reaches the next level.
Then I can do whatever I want.
Freddy could be wrong.
Yeah, it's just that he's been right
about everything else.
Hmm, like I said, pop star problems.
Well, they're safe with me.
Yeah, I believe they are.
- Yeah, you're gonna need that.
- Yeah.
- Come on.
- Uh, Oh...
Just... Will you just tighten
these bolts really quick,
and finish putting on the belts,
and I will be...
I'll be right back.
I've just got to check on...
Are you gonna come back, though?
I can't do this without you.
Yes, of course. I'll be back.
Bella!
You're supposed to make a noise there.
Am I too late to try on the slipper?
Every maiden in the land
is granted the opportunity.
Could that be her?
Ow!
The lass that I have waited
my whole life for?
Come! Come!
Please, present your foot.
What?
Your mole switched cheeks.
It happens to all the Snow women.
We just
don't like to talk about It.
Okay.
Uh...
Okay, yeah.
Bring your foot up. Good. And...
A perfect fit!
Okay, and now we get up.
We come up and get ready for the spin.
I have found you, my princess,
and you shall never wear rags again.
Come. Come! Come on!
Never fear. Your fairy godmother is here.
Let others see you as I do.
Twirl.
- Twirl.
- Come on.
- Flick the wrist like I showed you.
- Twirl!
Ahhh.
For crying out loud, people...
Fix this, please!
Now, let's take It from the top.
Bella?
Now where is she?
So, you put the mole...
Georgie? Okay, here we go.
Ow!
Georgie, what are you doing here?
Well, Tessa,
Reed was looking for you,
so I offered to help.
Oh, I can't believe I did that.
Um, right. Right.
I will, um... I, Tessa, will take it
from here. Thank you, Georgie.
You're welcome.
- Hi.
- HI.
- Sorry.
- You okay? You look a little bit flushed.
- No, you're okay.
Um...
Have you seen Bella? She's AWOL!
Uh, no, she'll be back.
She promised not to disappear again.
Yeah, right. So much for promises.
Where was I?
You know what? I think I...
I just saw Bella,
and I think I should probably
just go check on her for Freddy...
No, don't go, please.
I've got to go and perform In a minute.
Um, this will just take a second.
Be right back.
Okay.
There you are!
Divine! Hi.
Oh, I know what you are doing.
- You do?
- Yes.
- These eyes see everything.
- They do?
Hmm.
Oh, I know you have
your own little fantasies
about being up on stage,
but lurking around the VIP area,
Cinderella, is just sad
and, frankly, a little creepy.
Right, yeah, of course. I'm so sorry.
No more creepy. Understood.
Oh, good. Now where are those gowns?
- The gowns!
Where are the gowns?
Yes, I was just about to pick
the gowns up, actually. You can come with,
unless, of course, you don't want
to be seen In, you know, the service area.
Have them in the suite in five minutes.
You need to help us get dressed.
Yes, of course.
Sorry I'm late.
I had to find more contacts.
That's okay.
Is this almost over?
No, now I need to be
In three places at once.
Now that's what I call star power.
Twirl, girls. Twirl for Sparkles.
- Oh, Tessa, I have something for you.
- For me?
I didn't forget you, Tessa. There you go.
You can't go to a costume ball
without a costume.
Wow.
- Thank you, Divine.
- You're so welcome.
All right, girls, let the dazzling begin!
Stand up straight. Smile. Chest forward.
Out of my way, big baby!
There's a lot of Cinderellas here,
but you girls look the best.
Stand up straight, Olympia.
Hello.
On the behalf of the Halstons
and Royal Lagoons Resorts,
welcome to the VIP costume ball!
- First, one little question.
- What?
Is anyone in this room ready to get loose?
Okay, play the music!
Interesting choice of costume.
I'm a penguin.
Yes, you are.
Can you sneak away?
Uh, so we can finish the bike.
I'll waddle out somehow.
- Tessa?
- Yeah...
My hair broke.
You have to help me put It back together.
Five minutes.
How's Your mystery girl
working out for you?
She's talented, but she's flaky.
Oh, I'm sure
she has her reasons for that.
Yeah.
Maybe I just would prefer
someone I can trust.
Someone who's funny, likes to laugh,
smart, of course,
smarter than me, probably,
who's amazingly cute and waddles.
Um...
I think that should do it.
- You wanna try and start her up?
- No, do the honors.
Ah! You did it.
We did it. We totally did it.
What about Harper?
There you are. You're supposed to be
meeting with the Halstons right now!
Uh, oh, yeah.
Um, I lost track of time.
Can you give me one minute?
Oh, you need a minute?
By all means, yeah, take all the...
No, you can't have a minute!
We don't keep the big money waiting, Reed.
I'll call you later.
Let's go. Let's go.
Freddy.
The Halstons. Um, will Harper be there?
Yeah, she's flying out to surprise Reed.
I arranged It.
So they're together.
Oh, Tessa.
I know it must be a rush
being around a guy like Reed.
- He's about to become a huge star.
- I could care less about that.
Which is exactly
why Harper is so right for him.
Look, I don't know what Reed told you,
but I'm pretty sure he's gonna propose
by the end of the month.
What?
I'm sorry, Tessa, really. Sorry.
How could I have been so stupid?
I'm done. Done with the show.
I'm done with Reed,
and definitely clone with Bella Snow.
The show can't go on without Bella.
He's resourceful.
He'll figure something out.
Speaking of.
Look, this is about you.
Did you become Bella Snow to win a boy?
No.
- No, I became Bella Snow because I was...
- You were following your dream.
Freddy was a real wakeup call, Georgie.
I'm a nobody with just enough talent
to delude myself.
Tessa it's your decision,
but If you give up now,
you'll always wonder to your dying day,
what if?
God, I miss you.
I wish you were here, Dad.
Well, not exactly here.
Now, what would you do if you were me?
- Very good.
- Bravo.
Well done.
It's just... It's hard to be Cinderella
when I know my Prince Charming
is in love with someone else.
Get a grip, and focus on what's important.
Yeah, you're right.
Go back out there,
and show them who you are, okay?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Let's go. Okay.
Do you get what's going on?
- No.
- Ugh!
That's right. We're mean.
We don't like you. You're horrible.
Ah.
Georgie?
Divine.
Cheerio, Bella.
I knew you smelled like cookies.
Did you really think
you could get away with this'?
Athena has the blood of a star
running through her veins,
and she will take her rightful place.
Divine, please don't do this.
"Please don't do this, Divine."
Toodle-oo.
Divine, no. No, no, no! Divine, please!
Divine, please! Can someone hear me?
Come on, think, Tessa. Think.
Georgie, is Tessa all right?
She's not answering my calls or texts.
If you really care,
why don't you ask Freddy?
- She's the one.
- But how do we find her, My Prince?
We must search the land
to find the lovely Malden
whose delicate foot
fits this glass slipper.
Why isn't Bella in position?
I don't know. I've been waiting
to dress her In... Where's her costume?
Oh. Ah.
What is wrong with you?
Why are you so fat?
- Mom!
- Let me try.
- Uh-uh. Olympia, keep watch!
- Momma...
Put your arms through the thing!
Put your arms through!
Why can't I be Cinderella?
Because, Olympia,
you're just not good enough.
- Mom, wait.
- Your arms. Come on!
- Wait. Mom!
- What?
Who's gonna play my part?
Welcome to our humble home.
His Highness requests the presence
of all the ladles of the house.
My two daughters and I are...
Where's your sister, dear?
Who cares? Maybe, she's dead!
No, I remember. She's in her room.
Silly me! How could I forget?
I meant she's far, far away in Detroit.
Hold on! Hold on!
Here I am, Mother!
- .Just keep going, and find Bella!
- How could I stay In Detroit
when it's Royal Try On a Glass Shoe day!
Why waste your princely time
on ground beef
when you could have filet mignon?
Don't be afraid. I don't bite.
Well, maybe a little bit here and there.
Actually, I'm just all cuddles.
Go ahead. Ask my sister.
- That doesn't appear to be an option.
- Uh?
What is happening out there?
I'll show Mom I'm good enough!
Stop it! Stop!
Give me that!
Stop it! You're ruining everything!
You evil girl! Come back here!
- Alas, it does not fit.
- Are you sure, Prince?
Really, really sure.
Cram it in!
I don't care! No! Just do it!
Excuse me. I must go feed the horses.
Hello, buddy.
Okay, so I'm kind of
In a situation right now.
You've got to tell me which way to go,
sugar. That way or this way?
Oh.
Okay, here we go.
No, I don't care.
We're not gonna stop the show.
- Freddy
- No... Just do It. Do It!
What are you doing? I need you out there.
- First tell me what you said to Tessa.
- Tessa?
Reed, the show's a mess.
I can't find Bella...
- Stop it!
- What're they doing?
- I don't know. I don't care.
- This is Important!
There you are, Prince dear.
Get out here, or I will cut you!
- What did you say to her? Just tell me.
- Go! Out.
No. No, no, no.
Right, if there are
no other ladies in the house,
then we must take our leave.
Unless... Hark! Do you hear something?
Um...
Maybe?
I'm sure I must have heard a noise!
Oh, you're stepping on me!
Ow. Ow.
Really?
Am I too late to try on the slipper? Ow!
Oh. Hello.
Am I too late to try on the slipper?
No! Am I too late to try on the slipper?
Oh, my God! What has gotten into you?
Stop It! No, no, no!
I'm not going back out
until you tell me what you said to Tessa.
No! It's my shoe! I'm a princess!
I'm a princess!
Girls, you're not acting like ladies!
Let me go!
Okay, I may have said something about you
and Harper getting engaged. That's all.
Oh. Why, Freddy?
Why would you say that to Tessa?
Guys! Guys! Cover your mic!
All right, everybody!
Get ready for the new Cinderella!
You're on the verge of stardom.
Reed, I did It for you.
Look, I know you mean well, Freddy,
but you do not get
to make those calls for me!
Harper's just a friend.
I don't like her that way.
No!
Tessa, I mean she's sweet,
but what's the big deal?
The big deal is, for the first time
In my life, I think I'm In love.
Oh.
Bella.
Am I too late to try on the slipper?
Tessa.
You're Cinderella?
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
who I really was.
I never thought that a prince like you
could ever love a girl like me.
Not as sorry as I am
to have caused you any pain.
My adviser, Frederico, spoke not the truth
of my Impending nuptials.
Freddy totally lied
about me getting married to Harper.
I heard.
Sound travels quite well in this kingdom.
Please, try on the glass slipper.
I'd love to.
You know what, I don't need a shoe
to tell me what I really feel In my heart.
You're the one.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
Stop It! You're disgusting!
Never fear. Your fairy godmother is here.
Let the world see you as I do.
Twirl.
Whoa!
Yes! Come on!
Your fairy godmother does great work.
She really does.
- Call me.
- Thank you.
- That was incredible.
- HI.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Georgie, I don't know how to thank you.
You don't have to.
I thought you might need this.
You're the best.
What would I do without you?
Sorry, buddy. I messed up.
If you don't want me to be
your manager anymore, I'll understand.
No, of course I do.
Plus, you may even get the chance
to work with a talented new star.
Hey, Charming, let's bounce.
Tessa! Sweetie, we did it!
I know I can't take all the credit,
but it certainly wouldn't have happened
without me, right'?
Divine, you've been the best evil
stepmother a girl could ever ask for but...
Thank you.
I think it's definitely time for us
to part ways.
Call me!
So, where do you wanna go?
Everywhere.
At some point, we all come across
an exciting opportunity,
a new path that might scare us.
My advice.
Pop the clutch, pick the road,
and make your happily ever after
come true.
Sorry.
English - SDH